worldispnetwork.com 2012-06-07

# Privacy Policy - Web Hosting, Reseller Hosting, Domain Name - Host Department

Host Department, LLC ("Host Department") and each of its partner sites through which Host Department provides its services ("Partner(s)") agree individually to abide by this Privacy Policy with respect to all Host Department hosted services and Web pages. The terms "we" and "us" refer to each of Host Department and our Partners; provided, in no event shall either of Host Department or our Partners be liable for the other's breach of this Privacy Policy. Our Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available via a link at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested by Host Department and our Partners.   
   
This notice applies to all information collected on the Host Department Web site, or submitted to Host Department or any Partner at any time through any of our services on any Partner's Web site. Personally Identifiable Information - When visiting Host Department's or any Partner's Web site and signing-up for or using an Host Department powered service on a Partner's Web site, you may choose to supply Host Department and Partner with information that identifies you personally. This information may include your name and contact information, as well as other demographic or commerce related information.   
   
We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which it is intended. This may include administering a service such as email, chat, etc., completing an order, shipping a product, or contacting you if you have indicated your permission to do so. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent necessary to administer the services we offer. When we receive email, we use return email addresses to reply with the information requested. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. When supplying contact information to Host Department and Partner you can indicate your preference if you would like to be contacted to receive information and updates about our services or other information pertaining to Host Department or Partner. Information you submit to us will not be used for this purpose unless you indicate this as your preference. When supplying contact information to Host Department and Partner you can indicate your preference to participate in the Host Department program if you would like to receive special offers from other companies that we think may be of interest to you. Information you submit to us will not be used for this purpose unless you elect to participate in the Host Department program or otherwise consent. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and services, and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our Web site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women use a certain service, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals unless they indicated this as their preference by participating in the Host Department program. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

Host Department LLC will be the sole arbiter as to what constitutes a violation of this provision.  

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
   
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never contact those we actually know are under 13, and we never make the personal information of anyone we know is under 13 available to anyone outside of Host Department or Partner unless required to do so by law. No part of our Web site or services are intentionally structured to attract anyone under 13.   
   
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your password-protected account and selecting to update your "Profile" or "Personal Info." We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.  
   
Host Department and Partner consider email transmitted via our service to be the private correspondence between the sender and recipient. We will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of a user's private communications, except as required by law, to comply with legal process, if necessary to enforce the Service Agreement, to respond to claims that such contents violate the rights of third-parties, or to protect the rights or property of Host Department, LLC, our Partners, their third party service providers or others. By using the service you agree that technical processing of email communications is and may be required to send and receive messages, to conform to the technical requirements of connecting networks, to conform to the limitations of the Service, or to conform to other, similar technical requirements. By using the service you acknowledge and agree that Host Department, LLC, our Partners and their third party service providers do not endorse the content of any user communications and are not responsible or liable for any unlawful, harassing, libelous, privacy invading, abusive, threatening, harmful, vulgar, obscene, tortuous, or otherwise objectionable content, or content that infringes or may infringe the intellectual property or other rights of another.
